我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法
It took everything in my friends' power
才把我救回来  但我们的世界
to bring me back, and in doing so
也因此出现了新的威胁
our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
现在法院判决将艾伦先生
The court orders that Mr. Allen
送押至铁山监狱
should be remanded to Iron Heights Penitentiary.
-好好适应  -我没杀人
- Get comfortable. - I didn't kill anybody.
当然  这里所有人都是无辜的
Yeah, sure. Everyone's innocent in here.
特别是那个人  大块头先生
Especially that guy. Yeah, Big Sir
12个标记  12个超能力者
12 markers, 12 metas.
现在我们知道有多少
Now that we know how many there are,
我们可以直接去找他们
we can go right to them.
-我不想惹麻烦  -太晚了
- I don't want any trouble. - Too late.
谢了  我只是好奇你为什么帮我
Thanks. I was just wondering why you helped me.
因为你爸爸帮过我
'Cause your dad helped me.
他主刀救了我
He operated and saved my life.
塞西尔  你确定我们需要婴儿床吗
Cecile, are you sure we need a crib?
我以前都是把爱瑞丝扔到垫子上
I used to plop Iris on some cushions
然后就去睡觉了
and call it a night.
我很高兴你在养第一个孩子的时候
Well, I'm glad to hear you got all your parenting mistakes
已经把该犯的错都犯了
out of the way with your first kid.
我养得很好啊
I think she's turned out pretty good.
亲爱的
Oh, babe.
我不敢相信我已经这么胖了
I cannot believe I am so big already.
我怀琼妮的这个时候不是这样的
You know, I was barely showing at this point with Joanie.
我已经尽力了  你觉得怎么样
All right, best I got. What do you think?
-是不是  -是不是什么
- Are they? - Are they what?
太紧了
Too tight.
你刚才说我的衣服
Hey, you just said that you thought
显得很紧  是不是不好看
my clothes were too tight, Do I look bad?
什么  我可没说
What? I didn't say that.
那你说什么时候才能恢复正常是什么意思
What do you mean when is it gonna go back to normal?
我也没说这个啊
I didn't say that either.
看着我
Look at me.
-我没说话  -你别闹了
- My lips weren't moving. - What are you talking about?
我听见你  我
I heard you. I--
我还是能听见你
I can still hear you.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
为什么我能听到你的心里活动
- Why can I hear what you're thinking?
天哪  乔
Oh, my God, Joe...
我好像会读心术
I think I can read minds.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第十二集
心跳每分钟170下
Heartrate's 170 BPM,
羊水里也没有暗物质的痕迹
and there's no sign of dark matter in the amniotic fluid.
这么说孩子不是超能力者了
So the baby's not a meta?
不是  是个正常的宝贝
Nope, it's a perfectly normal baby...
女儿
Girl.
你刚才想说宝贝女儿
You were gonna say baby girl.
-我又有女儿了  -我要有妹妹了
- I'm having another daughter? - I'm gonna have a sister?
看来不用办宣布派对了
Well, I guess we can cancel the announcement party.
男孩  女孩  概率都一样
Boy, girl, that's 50-50.
我们测测你有多厉害吧
Let's test your skills for real.
我在想数字几
What number am I thinking of?
3  11
Three. Eleven.
25  又是3
Twenty five. Three again.
妙蛙种子
Bulbasaur.
-妙蛙种子是什么鬼  -太诡异了
- What the hell is a Bulbasaur? - That's so weird.
我这个时候怎么会想起神奇宝贝呢
Why would I be thinking about Pokemon at a time like this?
你绝对有心灵感应
Yep, definitely a telepath.
可怎么会呢
But how?
如果宝宝不是超能力者
If the baby is not a meta,
那我的超能力是从哪来的呢
then where did these powers come from?
不  我没在那辆公交车上
Nope, I wasn't on the bus.
我也没有被外星人绑架过
No, I was not abducted by aliens.
我也没有从我外婆那里继承什么神秘图腾
No, I didn't inherit a mystic totem from my grandma.
拜托  各位  你为什么还在想妙蛙种子
Really, guys? Why are you still thinking about Bulbasaurs?
他是最可爱的一个
He's the cutest one of all!
好吧  我觉得最大的可能是因为
Okay, my best hypothesis is this is actually triggered by
你最近妊娠期的状态
your latest phase of pregnancies,
可能在第一次粒子加速器爆炸时
and it's actually latent dark matter
你的大脑里就已经有
that's been in your brain since...
潜在的暗物质了
maybe the first particle accelerator explosion.
就像是妊娠糖尿病
Think of it like gestational diabetes.
不过这不是  糖尿病可以用胰岛素治疗
But it's not. You can fix that with insulin.
是的  但这是暂时的
Right, but it's temporary.
生完孩子后症状应该就没有了
I mean, the symptoms should recede after childbirth.
好了  你们单独谈谈吧
Okay, we'll give you guys a minute.
乔  你现在在想
Joe, you are literally thinking,
"我很担心塞西尔"
"I'm worried about Cecile."
我只是想你们母子平安
I just want you and the baby to be okay.
我知道
I know.
不过  或许这还是件好事呢
But, maybe-- maybe this will turn out to be a good thing.
我一直都很好奇你的脑袋在想些什么
I've always wondered what goes on in that head of yours.
塞西尔有心灵感应的超能力吗
Cecile's a telepath?
比起把艾伦从监狱里救出来
Well, that's way more important
这件事更重要
than getting Allen out of prison!
-并不是  -说得好  哈尔
- Not! - Sick burn, Hare.
请不要鼓励他
Please don't encourage him.
作为前囚犯  我可以告诉你们
As a former prisoner, I can tell you--
不  那是大猩猩监狱
No, that was gorilla prison.
大猩猩监狱是最惨的  它们朝你扔便便
Gorilla prison is worse. They throw their scat at you.
我可以告诉你们艾伦还坐在他的牢房里
I can tell you that Allen is sitting in his cell,
受着煎熬  而这个家伙
suffering, while this guy,
迪沃的计划丝毫未减
DeVoe, continues his plan unabated.
哈里  上周塞西尔已经提出了上诉
Harry, Cecile filed an appeal last week.
我们没有新证据  所以那不重要
We have no new evidence, so that doesn't matter.
卫星正在监视着迪沃一家
We have satellites on the DeVoes.
而他们几周都没有任何行动了
And they haven't made a move in weeks,
那也不重要
so that doesn't matter!
巴里现在在铁山监狱里  所以最糟的情况下
Well, Barry's in gen pop, so worst case,
他总是可以穿墙逃出去
he can always phase out,
或者我打开缺口带他出来
or I can breach him out.
然后他就会成为逃犯  话说  拉蒙
And then he'd be a fugitive. And by the way, Ramon,
我们为什么不能看到他在里面的情况
why do we not have eyes on him in there?
想从这里接入模拟摄像头
Hey, it's a pain trying to get into
是很困难的事  无论我怎么努力破解
an analog camera from here, no matter how hard I hack.
再更努力点破解
Hack... harder.
我们现在是一筹莫展
We're nowhere.
这个团队一筹莫展  而当初
This team is nowhere, and this is the team
这个团队都能把巴里永世神速力监狱里救出来
that got Barry out of a pantemporal speed prison,
现在却不能帮他逃出国家监狱吗
and we can't spring him from a county jail?
哈里  我们和你一样在努力想办法
Harry, we are working just as hard as you, okay?
没错  我很不愿意承认这点
And yes, it kills me to admit it,
但是我们现在遇到了阻碍
but we are at a roadblock,
所以巴里只能...
so Barry is just gonna have to...
坚持住
hold on.
我简直无法想像巴里正在经受的煎熬
I mean, I can't even imagine what he's going through.
看清楚了  哭吧小子们
Read 'em and weep, boys.
够了
That's it.
下一局我来洗牌
I'm dealing next round.
你有点可疑啊  艾伦
You know, there's something fishy about you, Allen.
我可疑吗  你企图在监狱里谋杀我呢
I'm fishy? You tried to murder me in jail.
如果你没法
Well, if you can't play cards
和企图谋杀你的人打牌
with somebody who tried to murder you,
那你永远别想在这打牌了
you'll never play cards in here.
我就知道我会后悔叫你来玩游戏
I knew I'd regret inviting you to this game.
你也许块头很大  但是你的表情出卖了你
You may be big, but you got no poker face.
又是同花顺吗
Deuces again?
我不玩了
Okay, I'm out.
-你不能拿走  -那是我最后一个布丁
- Hey, you can't take that. - It's my last pudding.
那你就不该把它扔进来赌  蠢蛋
Then you shouldn't have thrown it in the pot, dumbass.
蠢蛋
Dumbass?
玩忽职守的政客
Politician who gets caught with his pants down.
没错  我说你是蠢蛋
Yeah. I'd say you're a dumbass.
那也许我就把整个赌池都带走
Well, maybe I'll just take the whole pot then.
-两位  别这样  -别惹我  贝洛斯
- Guys, come on. - Don't screw with me, Bellows.
不然怎样  你要开枪打我吗
Or what? You're gonna shoot me?
对了  你只对手无寸铁的人开枪
That's right. You only shoot unarmed men.
你在看什么
What the hell are you looking at?
这真是你坐牢的原因吗
Is that really why you're in here?
你对手无寸铁的人开枪吗
You shot an unarmed man?
我不过就是个坏人罢了
Yeah, I'm just another bad guy.
给我走开
Now get the hell out.
如果我爸真的冒着生命危险去救你  那
If my dad really risked his life to save yours, then...
我不相信你只是个坏人
I doubt you're just another bad guy.
不如告诉我到底是怎么回事吧
why don't you just tell me what really happened?
保安遭到谋杀
昨晚在抢劫失败后
"Suspect was arrested last night
疑犯被捕
after a botched robbery.
水星实验室仓储管理处
在企图盗窃水星实验室货运板条箱时
While attempting to steal from a Mercury Labs shipping crate,
大卫·P·拉切特  外号大块头先生
"David P. Ratchet, alias Big Sir,
据称开枪打死了一名保安
allegedly shot and killed a security guard.
一名目击者称此为枪击事件
An eyewitness called in the shooting."
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你说的一切将成为呈堂证供
Anything you say can and will be used against you...
事前拉切特曾因打架被捕
Ratchet was previously arrested for fighting..."
被告被判有罪
唯一的法医证据
The only forensic evidence
是来自现场的子弹壳
were bullet casings from the scene
和你拥有的一把枪上的弹壳相吻合
that matched the cartridge of a gun you owned.
你该走了
Okay, time to go.
那样的枪支鉴定是会有错误的
Hey, firearm identification like that can have errors.
根本就是没用的科学
It's practically junk science.
我说你该走了
I said, time to go.
你没杀那个人是吗
You didn't kill that guy, did you?
现场还有另一个人
There was another guy.
体型和我一样
My size, my frame.
我听到枪声
I heard the shots.
我想救那个保安
I tried to save the guard.
错误的时间出现在错误的地点
Wrong place, wrong time.
你怎么不直接告诉我
Why didn't you just tell me that?
因为这根本无关紧要  艾伦
'Cause it doesn't matter, Allen!
对警察来说不重要
It didn't matter to the cops,
对我的律师  或是陪审团都不重要
not to my lawyer, or the jury.
他们看我一眼
They took one look at me,
就认定我是犯人了
and decided I was the guy.
那人可能还在逍遥法外
That guy could still be out there.
如果我是那人
If I was that guy,
我早就离开这个该死的城市了
I would've ditched this crap town a long time ago.
中城热爱她的英雄
Central City loves her heroes.
科德工业
我最了解  因为我是新市长
And I should know. I'm your new mayor.
但是我们都知道  在这座城市和
But we all agree, doing business in the city
超能力者打交道是有风险的
with meta-humans can be a little risky.
中城的科技企业
Technology companies in Central City
被打劫的次数是全国平均值的30倍
are robbed at nearly 30 times the national average.
仅仅排在星城之后  各位
That's second only to Star City, folks.
因此我很荣幸的宣布
Which is why I'm proud to unveil
科德工业最新的高级研究设施
Kord Industries' newest advanced research facility,
设计初衷是成为此类型中最安全的建筑
designed to be the most secure building of its kind,
装配着超高速运动检测系统
complete with super-speed motion detectors,
音波振动防御
sonic vibration defenses,
还有不会冻住的激光束
and laser beams that don't freeze.
相信我  不会有人能闯入这座建筑的
Believe me, no one is breaking into this building anytime soon.
我讨厌这座城市
I hate this city.
塞西尔  宝贝  你来这做什么
Cecile, hey, babe. What are you doing here?
我需要个帮手  她想来帮忙
Uh, I needed a helper, and, well, she wanted to help.
是啊  西斯科说你在办一个
Yeah. Cisco said you were working a case
研究室消失的案子
about an R&D lab that vanished.
我想也许我能帮着找出点线索
I figured maybe I could help dig up some clues,
鉴于我现在是超能力者了
now that I'm a meta.
宝贝  你不是超能力者
Babe, you're not a meta.
我能听到这里的每个人
I can hear every one of these people.
这里确实有暗物质的痕迹
Dark matter definitely left its mark here.
我也猜到了
I figured as much.
那个巡警  那边那个
That patrolman, right there,
他对妻子不忠
he is cheating on his wife.
我总是说绝对不要相信留小胡子的
Uh, never trust a moustache, I always say.
我就留小胡子
I have a moustache.
不  你是性感山羊胡  他是瘆人小胡子
No, you have a sexy goatee. He has a creeper moustache.
红领带  宝贝啊
Red tie... Oh, baby.
红领带可不怎么喜欢他的上司
Red tie does not like his boss very much.
她来这里的一路上都这样
She's been doing this all the way over here.
那边那个女的
And that lady right there.
乔  乔  她是个小偷
Joe? Joe, she is a thief.
小偷
Thief!
订书钉  她从办公室偷了好几个月了
Staplers, she's been stealing them out of her office for months now.
她都快把用品柜里的拿完了
She damn near cleaned out the supply closet.
宝贝
Baby?
我爱你  我觉得你有的
I love you, and I think it's great
这个新能力挺棒的  但是我...
that you have these new powers, but I--
你想让我走吗
Oh. You want me to go.
我不是想让你走
Uh, I--I don't-I don't want you to go.
不用不用  你只是想做你的工作
No-no-no, hey, it's just 'cause you wanna do your job.
我完全理解  去吧  阻止犯罪吧
I totally get it. Go. Stop crime.
-爱你  -爱你
- Love you. - Love you.
我能听到所有人  太有趣了
I can hear everyone. It's so fun!
我能找到最近的安保摄像头
Hey. The closest security cam I can find
在街对面的提款机上
is from an ATM across the street.
图像可能有些糟  不过...
The footage is choppy, but...
-看看这个  -他这是...
- Look at that. - Did he just...
凭空变出了一台雪佛兰
Pull a Chevelle out of nowhere.
我去查查这车牌号
I'm gonna run those plates,
看看能不能知道这家伙是谁
see if I can get an ID on the dude.
明白了
Copy that.
好  我接受付费
Yes, I'll accept the charges.
巴里
Hey, Barry.
所以  巴里请你请我们把这家伙弄出监狱
So, Barry asked you to ask us to get this guy out of prison?
巴里和这人交了朋友
Barry had gotten close to this guy,
他说自己是无辜的
who says he's innocent.
是认错人的原因
It was a case of mistaken identity.
我在《中城时报》里找到的文献提到
Well, from what I could find out on CCPN's archives,
大块头先生的案子确实有些疑点
Big Sir's case does sound a bit suspect.
十五年前  他因为枪击一个守卫被治罪
15 years ago, he was found guilty of shooting a guard,
被告射杀守卫被治罪
但是却没有明显的动机
but there was no apparent motive.
只有一名目击证人啊
Only one eyewitness?
研究证明列队辨认罪犯
Studies have shown that lineup composition,
口头和非口头引导
verbal, and non-verbal cues,
都会导致无意识的错误识别
can all lead to unintended false identifications.
这些都是很不错
Look, this is all just fantastic,
但我们不会真的去做吧
but we're not really gonna do this.
是啊  咱们只为救出一个人
Yeah, I mean, um, we've already got a lot on our plate
手头上已经有很多事了
just trying to free one innocent man.
我们都想放巴里自由
We all want Barry to be free,
但我们现在也没有什么其他事可做了啊
but I don't know that there's much else we can do right now.
咱们已经四面碰壁了
We kinda hit a wall.
我们可不会在办这个案子的时候
Well, we're not gonna get through that wall
-突破那些墙  -只是一个案子而已
- while we're working on this. - It's just one case.
是  但这是我们必须要接的案子
Yean, and it's a case that we have to take.
艾伦让我们保证过一件事
Allen has made one request of us
自从他入狱
since he's been incarcerated,
而这个请求甚至与他无关
and the request doesn't even involve himself.
我们得接下这个案子
We have to take this case.
有时候你的话有多少信服力值得商榷
It's unsettling how convincing you can be sometimes.
有辆雪佛兰的车牌号相符
I got a plate match on the Chevelle.
注册在一个
It's registered to a perp
有多次非法闯入前科的罪犯名下
who has multiple breaking and entering priors:
希尔伯特·伦丁
Sylbert Rundine.
为什么城里每个罪犯的名字
Why does every villain in this city have a name
听上去都像是漫画书里的
that sounds like it came out of a comic book?
一定是哪个名字的简写
He must go by something for short.
希  希尔比  博迪
Syl. Sylbie. Bertie.
这个案子咱们想怎么办
What do we wanna do about this case?
我爸  西斯科  拉尔夫
Well, my dad, Cisco, and Ralph
去盘问伦丁  我打给塞西尔
are gonna question Rundine, and I'm gonna call Cecile
看她能不能调出来大块头先生的案子卷宗
and see if she can pull up the case file on Big Sir.
你都不用说出来
You won't even have to say it.
博迪这名字你是说真的吗
Bertie? Were you for real with that?
赌5块钱一定是博迪
Yeah, bet you five bucks it's Bertie.
那咱们赌上了
You're on.
艾伦  你把我扫的灰扬起来了
Allen, you're stirring up my dust.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
我有个事和你说
Um, I've got some news.
我有些朋友
So, I have some friends
能在你的案子帮上忙
that I thought could help with your case,
而且他们同意帮忙
and...they've agreed to do it.
中城警局的朋友吗
CCPD cop friends?
不算是
Not exactly,
但如果有人
but, um, if there's anybody
能证明你是清白的  那就是他们了
that can prove you innocent, it's these guys.
因为他们做了超棒的工作为你洗白吗
'Cause they did a bang-up job of clearing you.
那并不是...我的案子
That's not really-- I mean, my--my case--
听着
Look...
告诉他们停手吧
just call them and tell them to stop.
我不明白
Uh, look, I don't understand
你为什么一点也不兴奋
why you're not excited about this.
你在宣扬的  是件危险的事
What you're peddling, it's dangerous.
什么危险
Wh--what's dangerous?
希望
Hope.
我在监狱呆了足够久  明白了
I've been in here long enough to understand that in prison,
希望是最危险的事
hope is the most dangerous thing.
等等  你是看了《肖恩克的救赎》明白的吗
Wait, did you get that from "Shawshank"?
不
No.
是监狱的岁月让我明白的
I got that from being in prison.
告诉你朋友
Tell your friends...
不要浪费时间了
to stop wasting their time.
希尔伯特·伦丁
Sylbert Rundine!
我们是中城警局
This is CCPD!
你是希尔伯特·伦丁吗
Are you Sylbert Rundine?
博特  伦丁
Bert...Rundine.
e不发音
The E's silent.
很接近了
So close.
我是乔·韦斯特警探  他们是我的同事
I'm Detective Joe West. These are my associates.
我们在调查一起抢劫案
We're looking into a robbery that took place.
想要问你几个问题
Wanted to ask you some questions.
-好呀  -你有一辆70年代产的雪佛兰吗
- Okay? - Do you own a 1970s Chevelle?
-曾经有  -我的天
- Well, I used to. - Oh, my glob.
这是国防高级研究计划局HTV-3X的模型吗
Is that a replica of DARPA's HTV-3X?
你不知道不要碰别人的玩具吗
Don't you know not to mess with another man's toys?
你指的是雕像吧
You mean figurines.
是的
Yes.
他是这个意思
Yes, he does.
这个模型堪称完美
This is a perfect replica.
它甚至有一个袖珍的自动巡航控制系统
It even has a tiny automatic navigation control system!
所以我才存不下钱
This is the reason I don't have any money in my savings.
我明白了
Oh, I get it.
这是你吗
Is this you?
对  很难相信吧
Yeah, hard to believe.
15年前  我是一个健身狂热者
15 years ago, I was a bit of a gym rat.
乔  很棒的雕像
Hey, Joe, pretty nice figurine.
先生们  我正打算出门
Well, gentlemen, I was just about to head out,
如果没什么问题
so if you guys are good here...
15年前
15 years ago,
你去过水星实验室吗
did you spend any time around Mercury Labs?
西斯科  带我们去小路
Cisco! Get us to the alley.
我去  他不会那么快吧
Damn. He wasn't that quick, was he?
你们去看看那里  我去街上看看
You guys check down there, I'll check the streets.
好
Okay.
大伙儿  他在这儿
Guys, he's here!
待着别动
Hey! Hold it right there!
感觉很怪
Oh, that feels weird.
乔  他要跑了
Joe, he's getting away!
看起来我们有大麻烦了
Seems we've got bigger problems.
-太  -滑稽了
- This is... - Ridiculous.
你们还好吗
You okay, guys?
我们还好吗
Are we doing okay?
我们看起来像还好吗
Does it look like we're doing okay?
我们现在五厘米高  凯特琳
We're two inches tall, Caitlin!
对  我现在看起来和西斯科一样矮
Yeah, I'm, like, Cisco's size now.
你眼中的世界是这样的呀
Is this how you always see the world?
可真有趣
Oh, that's really funny, man.
我看你的身体终于缩小到
I guess your body just finally shrunk down
和你大脑匹配的尺寸了
to a size that's proportional to your brain!
拉尔夫  你有没有试着伸到正常大小
Ralph, have you tried just stretching back to normal size?
我的背啊  天呐
My back! Jeez Louise!
或许我可以通过缺口带咱们离开这
Okay, you know what, maybe I can breach us out of here.
还以为
Really thought, uh...
我会跑得更远
I was gonna go farther than that.
几个手指
How many fingers am I holding up?
4个
Four fingers.
你这么小还是这么讨厌
You're no less annoying at that size.
各位  我有主意了
Hey, guys, I think I got something.
我不能定位雷·帕尔默和乘波号
So, I wasn't able to pin Ray Palmer or the Waverider,
但我可以联系到费利西蒂
but I was able to reach Felicity.
雷用矮星合金
So, Ray uses dwarf star alloy
矮星合金
为原子侠战衣中的
to power the shrinking capabilities
缩小超能力提供动力
in the A.T.O.M. Suit,
但十月十号
but on October 10th,
帕尔默科技最后贮藏的合金
Palmer Tech's last depository of alloy
被人从中城大楼中偷走了
was stolen from Central City's facility.
十月十号
October 10th,
那天巴里从神速力中出来
that's the day Barry came out of the Speed Force.
他撞击了大楼  然后撞了那个公交
So he hits the facility, then he hops on the bus.
矮星合金加上暗物质
So, dwarf star alloy plus dark matter
就形成伦丁的缩小能力
equals Rundine's shrinking powers?
不完全是  自然规律下并不能缩小
N--not exactly. Nature doesn't work to scale.
如果人类身体收缩
If the human body were to shrink,
就撑不起我们的骨架
we can't lift our skeleton.
伦丁的能力肯定是
So, Rundine's power must be able to shrink
缩小原子键之间的空隙
the space between atomic bonds.
缩小之后就能偷走
Miniaturize tech so you can steal it,
然后卖的时候再放大
and then make it big so you can sell it.
拉切特的审讯记录
Ratchet's trial records.
你真的认为那个缩小建筑的家伙
You really think the guy who shrunk that building
就是救巴里朋友所需要的那个人
is the same guy we need to free Barry's friend?
看
Well...I mean, look.
很容易搞混
Be easy to mistake them, right?
他们的确很像
I mean, they certainly had a resemblance.
他们抓了大块头先生一个月后
Rundine hit up a warehouse
伦丁盗窃了仓库
a month after they picked up Big Sir.
是个大巧合
Still, that's a big coincidence.
我还得强调
I keep saying it:
迪沃问题上没有巧合
There's no coincidences when it comes to DeVoe,
包括巴里的狱友
and that includes Barry's cellmate.
我不能这么和法官说啊
Well, I can't sell that to a judge,
所以如果我们想救出大块头先生
so if we wanna get Big Sir out,
我们需要收缩博士的供词
we are gonna need a confession from Dr. Shrinker.
矮星
Dwarfstar!
那到底是个啥
What the hell is that?
是我给他起的名字  矮星
Oh, that's what I'm naming him, see, Dwarfstar.
天呐
Oh, God.
得好久才能通过缺口逃出
Oh, it takes a long time to breach here.
谁把口香糖吐到地上了
Who spit gum on the floor?
我是个侦探
I'm a gum-shoe!
可不是鞋上的口香糖
Not gum on a shoe!
天呐  快把他取下来  快取下
Oh, my God, get him off, get him off.
你俩得进仓鼠笼
You guys are going in the hamster cage.
仓鼠笼
Hamster cage?
别扔  别扔
Eh, don't drop me. Don't drop me.
哈里
Harry...
这不是你的错
this is not your fault.
没错  但似乎
Yeah, but it kinda I--
别读我
Don't read my mind, okay?
-我现在在想什么  -天呐
- What am I thinking now? - Oh, God.
好吧  恕我失陪
Great. Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要建一个反极性矮星模型
I'm gonna go build a reverse polarity dwarfstar matrix.
好名字  雷·帕尔默
Great name, Ray Palmer.
电子退化子原子化器需要什么
What, was electron-degenerate sub-atomizer taken?
电子退
Electron-de--
你根本不懂哈里说的意思
Oh, you have no idea what Harry was talking about,
或者大家说的话
or what anyone around here is ever talking about.
我去给巴里打电话
I gotta call Barry.
好的
Okay.
我能听到你  爱瑞丝
I can hear you, Iris,
我和乔之间没有问题
and there is nothing wrong with me and Joe.
当然  当然
Right, yes, totally.
只是  如果你觉得
It's just that if you ever,
有什么问题的话
you know, think there is something wrong,
我知道一个人可以提供帮助
I--I know someone who could help.
说完啦
That's all.
我是莎伦·芬科尔医生
I'm Dr. Sharon Finkel.
谢谢您能这么快见我们
Thank you for seeing us on short notice.
-我们太幸运了  -当然
- Lucky us. - Of course.
我们今天来这的原因是
The reason that we're here today is,
我遇到了一些不常见的怀孕症状
I've been experiencing some unusual pregnancy symptoms.
我第一次怀孕时
You know, the first time I was pregnant,
很久以前了
it was a really long time ago,
从那时起就很奇怪
and things were very different at that point--
鸡蛋  面包  橄榄油
"Eggs, bread, olive oil"
我很抱歉  你在...
I'm sorry, are you--
列购物清单吗
are you making a grocery list?
鸡蛋
面包
橄榄油
当然不是
Of course not.
我不会...
I would not do--
跟我多说些
So...tell me more about
你经历的症状
the--the symptoms you're experiencing.
就像是
It's--it's almost as if
我变得知道
I have become aware
乔的想法
of Joe's thoughts.
-就像在读他的日记  -我的日记
- Like--like I read his diary. - My diary?
你怀孕使你能读乔的日记
Your pregnancy made you read Joe's diary?
你站他那边是什么意思
What do you mean you're taking his side?
我不选边站
I don't take sides.
你认为我错了
You just think that I'm in the wrong.
我绝不会认为...
I would never think--
-也许这个主意不好  -不不不  宝贝
- Maybe this was a bad idea. - No-no-no, no-no-no, babe.
不  我们还没...这里还没完事
No, we're not-- we're not done here.
治疗令你害怕
Therapy scares you,
你不喜欢这个女人听你的事
and you don't like this woman hearing all your business.
塞西尔  我...那不是真的
Cecile--I--that just-- that--that's not true.
现在你只想离开
And now you just wanna go.
你认为这整件事是在浪费时间
You think this whole thing is a waste of time?
塞西尔  够了
Cecile, stop.
你不停地在想粉红象
You're thinking about a pink elephant over and over?
你在试着屏蔽我
You're trying to block me out.
能让我问个问题吗
Can I just ask one question--
真的吗  粉红象
Really? A pink elephant?
你为什么要对我隐瞒你的想法
Why were you hiding your thoughts from me?
因为你逼我那么做的
Because you're making me do it.
什...
Wh--
塞西尔  我们重新在一起时  我保证过
Cecile, when we got back together, I promised you
我绝不会再对你有所隐瞒
that I would never keep any secrets from you again.
只是现在...
Except now, it--
我不得不那么做
it's like I have to.
他们找到他了
Hey. They found him.
他叫希尔伯特·伦丁
His name's Sylbert Rundine.
他被捕的一连串罪名跟你的很像
He's been arrested for a whole bunch of crimes like yours,
而且他也跟你长得很像
and he used to look just like you too.
你要出去了
You're getting out of here.
你的肩膀很结实
You have a hard shoulder.
昨天  我告诉你怎么回事
So, yesterday, I tell you what happened,
今天  你就找到那家伙了
and today, you find the guy.
-整件事很...  -闪电
- It happened in a... - Flash?
速度
Snap.
你们警察和被蒙蔽的眼睛
You cops and your blinders.
可能又抓错人了
Probably got the wrong guy again.
严格来说  他们还没抓住他
Well...technically, they haven't gotten him yet.
你瞧  有些事总是出错
You see? Something always goes wrong.
你为什么要搞得这么困难
Why do you have to make this so hard?
可以试着去相信
It--it's okay to believe.
是吗
Yeah?
你为什么这么容易相信
Why is it so easy for you to believe?
你知道我的爸爸曾在这
You know my dad was in here
为他没犯的罪服刑吧
for a crime he didn't commit, right?
你知道发生什么事了吗
Do you know what happened?
十七年后
After 17 years,
杀死我妈的人供认了
the man that killed my mom confessed.
我的爸爸可以回家了
My dad got to go home.
你为什么不能也有回家的机会呢
Why shouldn't you get to go home too?
-十七年吗  -是的
- 17 years, huh? - Yeah.
你认为他们会抓住伦丁
You think they'll catch Rundine?
你真的认为这会成真吗
You really think it's gonna happen?
我保证
I promise.
你会出去的
You're getting out.
马后炮地说
So, in hindsight,
我明白把你们放在仓鼠笼里
I can see how putting you guys in a hamster cage
可能挺羞辱人的
could be humiliating.
-你觉得呢  -我很抱歉
- You think? - I'm sorry for that.
郑重声明  这非常棒
For the record, this is awesome,
但为什么你们有个巨型积木组
but why do you guys have a giant LEGO set anyway?
这是我注定
It is a three- dimensional model
被未来扭曲版的巴里
of the place where I was predestined
残暴杀害的地方
to be brutally murdered
的三维模型
by a twisted future version of Barry.
那个家伙
That guy.
过了一年变化真叫大啊
But what a difference... a year makes.
你对我的火箭筒做了什么
What did you do to my bazooka?
我把你的火箭筒
Well, I turned your bazooka
变成展大火箭筒
into an embiggening bazooka,
用了我们从伦丁家
with the help of the dwarfstar alloy
偷走的矮星合金
we stole from Rundine's apartment,
然后改良了雷·帕尔默业余的图纸
and improving upon Ray Palmer's amateurish schematics,
念段咒语  展大火箭筒来了
presto-chango, embiggening bazooka.
现在  你等着...
Now, if you'll just hold on...
慢着  我们现在就要用吗
Whoa, whoa-whoa-whoa, we're gonna do this now?
当然啊
Well, yeah.
伦丁不见踪迹
Rundine's in the wind.
这两人太小个了  我们需要展大他们
These two are small. We need to embiggen them,
我需要释放无辜的人  所以...
and we need to free an innocent man, so--
首先  "展大"不是个词
Okay, first of all, "Embiggen" is not a word,
其次  我们不该先测试下吗
and second of all, shouldn't we test this first?
用我来测试
I'll be a test subject!
来吧  拿我测试
Come on! Take me!
-当然  为什么不  -就是要这种精神
- Sure, why not? - That's the spirit.
我们来吧
Here--here we go. And...
韦斯特
West?
你也许应该...
You should probably, um...
天啊  抱歉
Oh, God, yeah. Sorry.
倒数  三  二  一
And...three, two, one.
不行  还是微小
Nope. Still tiny.
我们这样正常吗
Hey, are we supposed to be doing that?
-天啊  -他们的细胞爆炸了
- Oh, no. - Their cells are exploding.
展大枪不管对拉尔夫和西斯科做了什么
Whatever that embiggening gun did to Ralph and Cisco
好像在原子水平上使他们不稳定了
seems to have destabilized them on an atomic level.
他们有多少时间
How long do they have?
按这个速度  我猜细胞完全爆炸
At this rate, I would guess complete cellular explosion
会在十小时内
within...ten hours.
老兄  监狱布丁
Oh, man, prison pudding
比外面的布丁好吃多了
is so much better than outside pudding.
显然是的
Obviously.
你的朋友有消息吗
Any news from your friend?
还没有
Um, no, not yet,
也许他们在忙着追踪伦丁
but they're probably just busy tracking Rundine.
那么老练的罪犯
Seasoned criminal like that
知道怎么让自己不被找到
knows how to not be found, you know?
好的  我明白
Yeah, I get it, man.
你出去之后有什么计划吗
You have any plans for when you get out?
我真的还没怎么去想
You know, I really haven't thought about it very much.
拜托  你肯定有些什么
Oh, come on, you've gotta have something
一直想做的事  像是做生意
that you've dreamed of, like opening a business
或是登上珠穆朗玛峰顶
or, uh, climbing to the top of Mount Everest,
-蹦极跳  -这不是电影  艾伦
- bungee jumping. - This ain't the movies, Allen.
-这是真实生活  -我...
- This is real life, man... - I--
现实是  没有任何人或事情
Reality is, I ain't got nobody or nothing
在外边等着我
waiting for me on the outside,
就算我成功出去
and even if I do get out,
最终大概也就是沦落到码头上
I'll probably end up at the docks anyway.
好吧  我这一生里有很长一段时间
Okay, look, I spent most of my life
爱着一个完全不在我层级上的女孩
in love with a girl who was way out of my league.
现在她是我的妻子了
Now she's my wife.
有时  事情的结果会像是电影一样
Sometimes, things do end up like in the movies.
甲居
Jiaju.
-再说一次  -甲居
- Come again? - Jiaju.
中国的小村庄
Tiny village in China.
漂亮的地方  非常僻静
Beautiful place. Very secluded.
僧侣都起誓沉默
Monks all take a vow of silence.
犯人艾伦
Inmate Allen...
借一步说话
a word?
好
Yeah.
看来你交新朋友了
I see you've made a new friend.
是的  我想是的
Yeah. I guess I have.
我觉得挺有意思
I find that interesting,
尤其是我刚被要求
especially since I was just asked to turn over
把犯人拉切特的案卷
Inmate Ratchet's case file
交给替你辩护的地检官
to the D.A. who represented you for your trial.
巧合
Coincidence?
不是每个待在这里的人都该待在这里
Not everyone that's in here deserves to be in here.
你听过亚伦·米勒这个名字吗
You ever heard of the name Aaron Miller?
-没有  -米勒曾是这里的犯人
- No. - Miller was a prisoner here
他在法律图书馆学习
who took to studying at the law library.
有一天  米勒先生决定
One day, Mr. Miller decided to take on
替他的犯人同伴上诉
the appeal of a fellow inmate's case.
当他始终没能成功时
When he was invariably unsuccessful,
那个犯人同伴
that fellow inmate...
把米勒先生捅死了
stabbed Mr. Miller to death.
你的朋友可能长得像个人
Your friend may look like a man,
但他无疑是个魔鬼
but he is unquestionably a monster.
这里的所有人都是魔鬼
Everyone here is a monster.
如果你坚持继续招惹他们
And if you insist on continuing to bait them,
我向你保证
I guarantee you,
你会受到伤害
you will get mauled.
好吧  小心烫
All right, coming in hot.
你不必那么做的
Oh, hey, you didn't have to do all that.
我没有继承我父亲的厨艺
Listen, I did not inherit my dad's skills in the kitchen,
但泡一杯脱因花草茶我还是会的
but a decaf herbal tea, that I can do.
如果你不介意的话
So, if it's okay with you,
我想能不能跟你谈谈乔的事
I just was wondering if I could talk to you about Joe.
当然  我不介意的
Um, yeah. Of course it's okay.
亲爱的  不是那种事
Oh, no, honey, it's--it's not about that.
我们在那个部分完全没问题
We have zero problems in that department,
你可以看得出来
as you can tell.
好吧
Okay.
信息量太大  但没事
TMI, but okay.
我真的认为能读他的心
I really thought being able to read his mind
会使我们的感情更强  而不是分离我们
would make our relationship stronger, not push us apart.
我爸爸对你的新超能力
Well, how does my dad feel
有什么感觉
about your new powers?
他觉得需要一段时间去适应
He thinks it's gonna take a little getting used to.
是的  但他的感觉呢
Yeah, but how does he feel?
我们都知道我爸爸认为
Look, we all know that my dad thinks
自己是个很酷的神秘男子
that he's this cool, grounded man of mystery,
但我们都知道其实他只是个...
but we all know that he's actually just--
-柔弱的人  -柔弱的人
- A big softie. - A big softie.
但如果你真的要跟我爸爸亲近
But if you really want to get closer to my dad,
就不要再专注在他的想法
you need to stop focusing on what he's thinking
而是搞明白他的感觉
and find out what he's feeling.
也许我们可以用生化疗法
Maybe we could use a biochemical treatment
以脑下垂体为目标
and target the pituitary glands?
灌入大量人类生长激素
Flood them with human growth hormones?
不  那会加快他们的...
No, that will just accelerate their d--
把情况变得更糟
it'll make things worse.
-各位  -怎么了
- Guys? - What?
-各位  -说吧
- Guys? - Yeah?
-各位  -怎么了
- Guys! - What?
小拉尔夫要去小男孩洗手间
Little Ralphie needs to use little boys room.
你不是才去过吗
Didn't you just go?
现在我膀胱的大小
My bladder is literally the size
跟蜂鸟的差不多
of a hummingbird's right now.
来吧  凯特琳
Come on, Caitlin.
带小小人去小小便吧
Help a wee fellow take a wee-wee?
-你能不能  -我吗
- Can you... - Me?
我才不要碰他
Well, I'm not touching him.
好吧  我带你去
Fine, I'll take you there,
但你得自己找路出来
but you have to find your own way out.
谢谢
Thank you.
可以直接尿在草丛里
Could've just gone in the bushes.
恶心
Gross.
展大火箭筒让我们不稳定了  对吧
The embiggening bazooka made us unstable, didn't it?
对  不  什么  不是
Yeah--no. What? No!
你为什么要这么说
Wh--why would you say that?
你都表露在你脸上了
I can see it all over your face.
-什么  -你的脸很大
- What? - Your face is huge.
我是在超大屏模式下看你的表情
I'm watching your emotions on IMAX.
好吧  这...
Yeah. Yeah, this--
这事本该是轻松完成的  好吗
this was supposed to be an easy W, all right?
轻松的胜利
An easy victory.
我们只需要抓住伦丁
All we had to do was capture Rundine.
连这个都无法为艾伦做到
Couldn't even do that for Allen.
-好吧  你尽力了  -但我失败了
- Okay, so, you tried. - Yeah, and I failed,
因为我很愚蠢  好吗
because I'm stupid-- --all right?
太愚蠢地去帮艾伦的朋友
Too stupid to help Allen's friend,
太愚蠢地去救治你  太愚蠢地去阻止迪沃
too stupid to fix you, or too stupid to stop DeVoe.
你这是干什么
Ow! Wh--what was that for?
相信我  我要是可以就会给你胳膊一拳
Believe me, I'd punch you in the arm if I could.
我知道你不习惯对付
Look, I know you're not used to going up against
比你聪明的人  比如迪沃
someone you can't outsmart, like DeVoe,
但如果你觉得你太愚蠢
but you really are stupid
那你就真的很愚蠢
if you think you're too stupid.
你要帮巴里  你要让他恢复自由
You wanna help Barry? You wanna free him?
跳出困住你的框框  解除我们的收缩
Get out of your own way and unshrink us.
你不是收缩  好吗
You weren't shrunk, all right?
他的超能力不是这个  他的超能力...
That's not how his powers work! His powers...
不只是...
Work by not just...
消除原子之间的空间
removing the space between the atoms,
同时也取出重力粒子
but also taking out the gravity particles
和暗能量
and the dark energy,
所以当他把物体展大时...
so that when he embiggens an object...
他把他获取的能量组合
He's refilling it with the same combination
-充填回去  -是的
- of energy he extracted. - Yes.
哈利  如果你要修复我们
Harry... if you wanna fix us...
我们要把你放回伦丁的射线里
We need to put you back in Rundine's line of fire.
中城气象局
Central City's Weather Services Agency
总是采用尖端的雷达技术
is always on the cutting-edge of radar technology,
所以我非常兴奋地向您展示
which is why I'm so excited to show you the newest addition
我们最新版的静止飞舰
to our stationary airship fleet.
现在  让我们走近看看
Now, let's go take a closer look.
我们还有二十分钟会爆炸是什么意思
What do you mean we only have 20 minutes until we explode?
其实还有十八分钟
Actually, it's only 18 minutes
你身体的平衡就会完全不稳定
before your equilibrium totally destabilizes.
20分钟内你会爆炸
You're gonna blow up in under 20 minutes,
除非我们让你再曝露在伦丁的能量冲击波下
unless we re-expose you to Rundine's energy blasts, okay?
脸部识别系统
Okay, so a facial recognition
刚发现他出现在气象局机场
just picked him up at Weather Services Airfield.
他可能想出城
I think he's trying to skip town.
我留在这里设法找出解药
Okay, I'm gonna stay here and try and figure out a cure.
先生你得离开
Hey. Sir, you need to leave.
博物馆已经关闭了
The museum is closing for the day.
我知道
I know.
我只是觉得这个摆在我架子上会很漂亮
I just thought this would look great on my shelf.
红色警报  大家撤离
Red alert! Red alert! Everyone evacuate!
开快点  我们得开快点
Gotta go faster. We gotta go faster.
你想由你来开吗
Do you wanna drive this thing?
有点想  拉蒙  记得
Kinda do. Ramon, remember,
当伦丁试图收缩货车时
when Rundine tries to shrink the van,
你得进入他的冲击波里
you've got to get in the path of his blast.
-明白吗  -收到
- Do you understand? - Copy that.
我们现在前往停机库
We're heading into the hanger now.
各位
Uh, guys?
我觉得他看到我们了
I think he sees us.
你不会再变大了
You're not getting big again.
我去左边  你去右边
I'll go left, you go right!
哈利  从侧面夹击他
Harry, try flanking him.
我们从另一边过来
We're gonna come around the other side.
收到
Copy that.
机动规避  机动规避
Evasive maneuvers! Evasive maneuvers!
我知道  我正在做
I know, I'm doing it.
天啊
Oh, boy.
我们得设法让他冲咱们攻击
We've gotta figure out how to get him to fire at us.
弃机
Abort!
-我们掉的太快了  -想点轻松的
- We're going too fast. - Think light thoughts.
我在想你怎么差点害死我们
I'm thinking how you nearly got us killed.
想得更轻松些
Think lighter!
斯诺  告诉我你好了
Snow, tell me you got something.
解药还没好
The cure is not done yet.
还有一分钟他们就核爆炸了
Only one minute till the boys go nuclear.
-我不要爆炸  -我们怎么做
- I don't want to explode. - What do we do?
启动备用计划
We go to plan B.
我要把你收缩到亚原子水平  小子
I'm gonna shrink you down to the subatomic level, boy.
是吗
Oh, is that right?
你有本事来试试看啊
I'd like to see you try.
我又变大了
I'm big again!
提醒我别再跑进去
Remind me to never again breach into
哈利发臭的口袋
any of Harry's stankin' ass pockets!
再次抱歉我踩了你
Hey. Sorry again about stepping on you.
你帮我省了去找脊椎按摩师的麻烦
Hey, you saved me a trip to the chiropractor.
我想是的
Yeah, I guess so.
你做到了
You did it.
我想我做到了
Yeah, I guess I did.
你有权保持缄默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的一切
Anything you say can and will be used
将作为呈堂证供
against you in a court of law.
你有权找律师
You have the right to an attorney.
如果你请不起律师  将提供一名给你
If you cannot afford one, one will be provided for you.
双手放在身后
Hands behind your back.
伦丁
Rundine...
十五年前
15 years ago,
你有抢劫水星实验室仓库吗
did you rob a Mercury Labs warehouse?
现在对我们供认
Give us your confession now,
我保证地检官会跟你谈协议
and I guarantee the D.A. will cut you a deal.
水星实验室
Mercury Labs...
是拉切特被错认的那个案子
that's the one that Ratchet got fingered for.
那家伙被捕时我笑开怀了
I laughed so hard when that guy got arrested.
你想要供认[忏悔]
You want a confession?
找牧师吧
Find a priest.
我宁愿堕落
I'd rather rot.
好吧  谢谢
Yeah, all right. Thanks.
乔  稍等一下  好吗
Hey, Joe, just hold on a second, all right?
不是好消息吧
Ain't good news, is it?
伦丁不供认
Rundine won't confess.
我的朋友尽了一切努力
My friends tried everything,
地检官给了她能给的所有协议  但...
I mean, the--the D.A. offered every deal she could, but--
我很抱歉  老兄
I'm so sorry, man.
这里的事你说的都没错
Look, you were right about everything in here.
我向你保证了...
You know, I-I made you a promise and...
我却让你失望
I let you down.
该死的笨蛋
You damn idiot.
你没有让我失望
You did not let me down.
我忘记了希望的感觉
I forgot what hope felt like.
这不是坏事
It's not a bad thing.
我们再见  小子
I'll see around, kid.
抱歉
Hey, sorry.
没事  巴仔
It's okay, Bar.
我只是想谢谢你的努力
I just wanna thanks for trying, you know,
我很抱歉让你白忙了
and I'm sorry to send you on this goose chase.
巴里  你待的地方到处都是墙
Barry, that place you're in is full of walls.
当你撞上其中一面墙
When you hit one of those walls,
你找到穿过它的方式
you find a way to get through it.
不要失去信念
Don't lose your faith.
太多人指望着你
There's too many people counting on you,
外面和里面
out here and in there.
中国  甲居
有时你会得到电影里的结局
不
Nope.
我们都舒心之前谁也别走
Nobody leaves until we're both good again.
好吧
Okay.
你要我怎么做  塞西尔
What do you want from me, Cecile?
我想知道为什么我有这些超能力
I wanna know why me having these powers
让你非常苦恼
is so upsetting to you.
你有超能力  直接读我的心吧
You have the power. Just read my mind.
不不不  我读你的想法
Uh-uh, no, no-no, me reading your thoughts
才使我们陷入这种局面的
is what got us into all of this.
我想知道你的感觉
I want to know how you feel.
塞西尔  你能读我的想法
Cecil, you being able to read my...thoughts,
让...
it--
让我有我不喜欢的脆弱感
it makes me feel vulnerable in a way that I don't like,
你能听到我的所有害怕
you being able to hear every scared...
愚蠢的想法
dumb thought of mine.
我只是不想...
I just don't...
让你看见那样的我
want you seeing me like that.
但是我绝不会因为你脑中
But I would never think less of you
闪过的一时想法而小瞧你
for the thoughts that cross your mind.
怎么不会呢
How could you not?
好吧
Okay--
乔  你的埃丝特祖母面条味道很糟糕
Joe, your grandma Esther's noodles, they taste terrible.
它们真的糟透了
Uh, no, they are terrible.
那个女人完全不该跟锅子搅和
That woman had no business ever messing with the wok.
好吧
Okay.
我觉得我一生都把分号
And I think that I have been using semi-colons wrong
用错了  导致我认为
for my entire life, which leads me to believe
我甚至不知道分号到底是什么
that I don't even know what a semi-colon actually is.
而且  我想买条新裤子  因为...
Also, I would like to buy a new pair of pants, 'cause...
但我还没买  因为我害怕去商店
But I haven't yet, 'cause I'm afraid to go into the store,
因为我觉得店员会审视我
'cause I think the salesperson is gonna judge me,
因为  说真的  连我都觉得
because, truthfully, even I think
我有点发疯
that I am just a little bit crazy
这把年纪了还要生孩子
for having another baby at this age.
宝贝
Oh, baby...
你没发疯
You're not crazy.
你刚说的话有点...
That speech you just gave w--was a little--
你没疯
You're not.
那些是我的害怕  愚蠢
Those were my scared, dumb,
脆弱的想法
vulnerable thoughts.
你会小瞧我吗
You think any less of me?
当然不会
Of course not.
听着
Look...
我无法保证我不再读你的心
I can't promise you that I'm gonna stop reading your mind.
我真的还不知道这超能力怎么用的
I--I don't even really know how this all works yet.
但我可以向你保证
But I can promise you
你的任何想法不会改变我对你的看法
that nothing you ever think will change my opinion of you.
就算你没那么想
And even when you're not thinking it,
我知道
I know...
你是我勇敢  杰出
that you are the brave, brilliant...
非常英俊的爱人
devastatingly handsome man that I love,
而我听到你最多的想法是
and the one thought I hear you have the most
你也爱我
is that you love me too.
我爱你
And I do.
根据我做的扫瞄  拉尔夫和西斯科的细胞
Well, based on my scans, Ralph and Cisco's cells
已经重组和恢复稳定了
have reformed and restabilized.
我可以证实我的膀胱已经完全恢复正常
I can attest my bladder is completely back to normal.
今天的第四杯大杯
Fourth Big Gulp today.
想念我们把他捡起来
I miss when we could just pick him up
带出房间的时刻
and carry him out of the room.
你刚才错过了对德比的挖苦
Hey, uh, you just passed up a dig at Dibny.
你确定没事吗
Sure you're all right?
我们重新翻出一个冤枉了人的案子
You know, we reopen a case against an innocent man,
然后  居然偶然发现了真凶
and, oh, somehow stumble upon the actual culprit,
而这个凶手  他之所以有超能力
a culprit who, by the way, has meta-human powers
我们要负部分的责任
that we are partially responsible for...
就像你说的  只要牵扯到迪沃
It's like you said: There are no coincidences
和这些巴士超能力者的事就不是巧合
when it comes to DeVoe and these bus metas.
迪沃在干什么  他有什么动机
What's DeVoe doing? What's his...motive?
他想要希尔伯特·伦丁被监禁
Does he want Sylbert Rundine incarcerated?
还是让大块头先生放出来
Or to have Big Sir set free?
或者是让我和西斯科变成微型超能力者
Or for Cisco and I to become itty-bitty meta-humans?
好吧  不管他有什么计划
Well, whatever his plan is,
我们都会搞明白
we'll figure out.
-我们会阻止他  -然后让巴里回家
- We're gonna stop him. - And bring Barry home.
然后让巴里回家
And bring Barry home.
站起来  犯人
On your feet, inmate.
有事吗  监狱长
Is there a problem, warden?
如你所知  犯人拉切特
As you know, Inmate Ratchet
昨晚神秘失踪
mysteriously disappeared last night.
你认为他去哪里了
Where do you think he went?
我没头绪
Well, I couldn't say.
为了找到犯人拉切特
In an effort to locate Inmate Ratchet,
我翻看了安全摄像头
I reviewed the security camera footage.
你知道这一区不是只有
Did you know the oscillating cameras
来回摆动的摄像头吧
aren't the only ones in this wing?
当你开始给
Once you started stroking
犯人拉切特自由的希望时
Inmate Ratchet's hopes of freedom,
我在你的囚室安装了摄像头
I had a camera installed right by your cell...
当我查看那个摄像头时
and when I checked that camera,
我发现了你的真实身份
I learned who you truly are.
我不知道你在说什么
Um, I don't know what you're talking about.
让我明说吧
Then let me be specific.
你是闪电侠
You are the Flash.
否认或者逃跑是没用的
There's no use denying it or trying to run.
你肯定已经感觉到了我混在
You're clearly already feeling the effects of
你吃得很享受的点心里的迷药效果
the drug cocktail I put in that snack you so seem to enjoy.
为什么  你为什么这么做
Why? Why would you do this?
我警告过你
I did warn you...
在这的所有人都是魔鬼
Everyone in here is a monster.
这样就行了
That'll be all.
你说我准备好做交易时就打给你
You said to call you when I was ready to do business.
你好  监狱长
Hello, Warden.
你还有别的鱼卖我吗
Do you have another fish to sell me?
有
I do...
而且还是条大的
and it's a big one.